lookatwhatimade.net 2019-06-30

# Disclosure and Privacy Policy ⋆ Look At What I Made

Last updated: May 2018

Look At What I Made (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the http://www.lookatwhatimade.net website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.**

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name and email address (“Personal Information”).

**Log Data**

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service’s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

You can read more about the specific cookies we use, and how to opt out, [HERE](http://www.lookatwhatimade.net/privacy-policy/cookie-policy/).

**DoubleClick Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other web sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ "Google Ads Settings") web page.

**Behavioral Remarketing**

Look At What I Made uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

  * **Google** Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads "Google Ads Settings") page. 

Google also recommends installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on") for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the [Google Privacy & Terms](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ "Google Privacy & Terms") web page.

**Amazon Affiliate**

Lookatwhatimade is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com and Amazon.co.uk.

**Other Affiliate Programs**

  * Commission Junction (including Annie’s)
  * Affiliate Window (including Deramores)
  * Sharasale (including Craftsy and Leisure Arts)

**Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

**Compliance With Laws**

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or in accordance with an order of a court of competent jurisdiction, or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

**Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. As such we make no warranties as to the level of security afforded to your data, except that we will always act in accordance with the relevant UK and EU legislation.

**International Transfer**

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United Kingdom and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United Kingdom and process it there.

Your continued use of this website will be seen as Implied Consent to this Privacy Policy.  Your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

In the event that a dispute arises with regards to the international transfer of data, you agree that the courts of England and Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction over the matter.

**Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

**Jurisdiction**

This Policy shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of England and Wales, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://www.lookatwhatimade.net/contact/).
